<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CWRURide</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="driver">Driver</string>
    <string name="passenger">Passenger</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select Date</string>
    <string name="select_date_day">Day</string>
    <string name="post_a_ride">Post a Ride</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="ride_board">View Ride Board</string>
    <string name="request_board">View Request Board</string>
    <string name="my_trips">My Trips</string>
    <string name="trip_history">Trip History</string>
    <string name="buzzwords">Buzzwords</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="post_this_ride">Post this ride?</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="account_detals">Account Details</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="edit_payment_options">Edit Payment Options</string>
    <string name="car_info_label">Car Information</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>


    <string-array name="timelist">
        <item>0:00</item>
        <item>0:30</item>
        <item>1:00</item>
        <item>1:30</item>
        <item>2:00</item>
        <item>2:30</item>
        <item>3:00</item>
        <item>3:30</item>
        <item>4:00</item>
        <item>4:30</item>
        <item>5:00</item>
        <item>5:30</item>
        <item>6:00</item>
        <item>6:30</item>
        <item>7:00</item>
        <item>7:30</item>
        <item>8:00</item>
        <item>8:30</item>
        <item>9:00</item>
        <item>9:30</item>
        <item>10:00</item>
        <item>10:30</item>
        <item>11:00</item>
        <item>11:30</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>12:30</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpList">
        <item>Posting a Ride</item>
        <item>Accepting a Ride</item>
        <item>Starting and Ending a Ride</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="posting_ride">In order to post a ride, start by clicking the post button ride on the bottom of the
                                main page. This will bring you to the Post a Ride page. Here you can input all
                                The information about your ride including the pick-up and drop-off locations,
                                date, time and if you will be the driver or the passenger. After clicking the
                                driver or passenger button at the bottom of the page, a confirmation dialog will
                                appear. You can choose to close the dialog and adjust your ride or you can confirm
                                the post and the ride will appear in the appropriate ride and my trips boards.
    </string>
    <string name="accepting_ride">In order to accept a ride you must first decide if you wish to be a passenger or a driver.
                                    If you would like to be a driver, click on the available requests tab from the left slide
                                    menu of the main page. If you wish to be a passenger, click on the available rides tab on
                                    the same slide menu. After clicking on your desired tab, a page with a table of rides will
                                    open. The table will show the time, date and description of the ride along with the rating
                                    of the user who posted it. By clicking on a row in the table, a dialogue will open with more
                                    detailed information about the ride. In this dialogue you can choose to cancel and continue
                                    looking for rides or you can accept the ride which will enter your my trips board.
    </string>
    <string name="start_end">In order to start a ride you must go to your my trips page and click on the ride you would like
                                to start. When you click on a ride a dialogue will open giving you the option to start a ride
                                or to cancel and close the dialogue. Both the driver and the passenger need to start the trip.
                                After starting the trip, if you click on the ride again, the start ride button will become an
                                end ride button. Clicking this will end the ride and once again, both the driver and the passenger
                                need to end the ride. Ending the ride will open up the review page.
    </string>
    <string name="endride">End Ride</string>

</resources>
